stylemoi.nu 2017-05-15

# Privacy Policy at Style Moi

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Style Moi (“StyleMoi”, “Style-Moi”, “style moi”, “we”, “our”, “us) is a trading name of Pando Corporation. We respect the privacy rights of its online visitors (“you”, “your”, “yours”) and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about them. We have adopted a     corporate wide Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information that you provide us with.

The following information is provided by Style Moi to enable our online visitors to be fully informed of our Privacy Policies. By visiting stylemoi.nu, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions.

•          What Data do we collect from you and how?

•          What about Cookies?

•          How your Data may be used, including anyone it might be shared with

•          Direct Marketing opt-in and opt-out provisions

•          How you can access and if necessary, change the Data Style Moi maintains

•          Safeguarding your Data

•          Retention of Data

•          Where and how to ask questions or file complaints

If you are under 16, we require that you inform a parent or guardian about Style Moi’s Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions as well as requiring their consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions before registering or placing an order with Style Moi.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link and Style Moi is not responsible for any personal information you submit to third parties via our website. Please ensure that you read the Privacy Policy of such other companies or organizations before submitting your details.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU AND HOW?**

Style Moi collects personal information which may contain personal data as defined under the Hong Kong Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Cap. 486) as amended from time to time (“Data”) in several ways when you place an order or register for a service offered by Style Moi. By registering, you are consenting to the collection of your Data. If an order is placed with us, we need to hold your Data including your name, email address, phone numbers, home address, shipping and billing address(es) so that we can process and fulfill your order.

We do not save or store any of your card details on our site. All payments are processed by PayPal. Additionally we may also obtain your Data as a result of authentication or identity checks. Sometimes we may ask for your telephone number. This number may be given to our courier for delivery services. These details allow us to process your order and to let you know the status of your order.

**WHAT ABOUT COOKIES?**

Our site uses cookies (very small files that are sent by us to your computer or other access device) which we can access when you visit our site in future.

There are four types of cookies:

Website functionality cookies

These cookies enable you to browse the website and use our features such as shopping baskets and wish lists

Website analytics cookies

We use these cookies to measure and analyse how our customers use the website. This allows us to continuously improve our website and your shopping experience.

Customer preference cookies

When browsing or shopping online, the website will remember preferences you make (for example your user name, language or location). This makes your browsing experience simpler, easier and more personal to you.

Targeting cookies or advertising cookies

These cookies are used to deliver adverts relevant to you. In addition, they limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as helping us measure the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns.

By using our website you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device and access them when you visit the site in the future.

If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the help and support area on your internet browser for instructions on how to locate the file or directory that stores cookies. Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at www.AboutCookies.org. Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site.

**HOW YOUR DATA MAY BE USED, INCLUDING ANYONE IT MIGHT BE SHARED WITH**

Style Moi may use your Data for the processing of orders, payments and to provide you with a personalized shopping experience. We will also use your Data to fulfill and deliver your orders and manage your account. Data that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. Your Data may be transferred (within or outside Hong Kong) with the following parties:

o          other trading divisions within Style Moi Limited;

o          our servers located in the United States for storage and backup;

o          where there is a legal obligation to do so, to any relevant government, judicial and regulatory body; and

o          Third Party Service Providers as detailed below

We may also use your Data to send you marketing updates but only ever in accordance with your preferences (as detailed in the next section). We do not sell your Data to third party marketing companies.

We do collect information about site traffic, sales, wish lists, and other commercial information which we may pass on to third parties but this information does not include any Data which can identify you personally.

Finally, we may use your Data for our internal and demographic studies, together with non-personal data to monitor customer patterns so we can consistently improve our site design to better meet our visitors’ needs.

From time to time Style Moi may employ third party business partners to collect Data on Style Moi’s behalf and to assist Style Moi with its [data hosting, email, debt collection (only if applicable) and customer services (“Third Party Service Providers”). In such cases, these Third Party Service Providers will be subject to confidentiality agreements and instructed by Style Moi to comply fully with the Style Moi Privacy Policy.

**DIRECT MARKETING OPT-IN AND OPT-OUT PROVISION**

We intend to use your Data in direct marketing and we may not so use your Data unless we have received your consent (which includes an indication of no objection). We would like to use the Data in our records including your name, [phone number, email and/or correspondence address ] to send you marketing materials. When you register, you will be given the option to opt-out of subscribing to our regular update service which will send you Email and direct mail alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions. Such alerts may include marketing information about clothing, bags and accessories offered by Style Moi and our subsidiaries, or products and services offered by our selected business partners.

We do not sell or otherwise pass your Data to third parties for their marketing purposes but the Data may be provided to subsidiaries and associated companies of Style Moi for informing you of their marketing information about clothing, shoes, bags and accessories. Marketing communications you subscribe to will only be sent by Style Moi.

At all times, we will offer you the opportunity to unsubscribe out of any service or update to which you have subscribed, if you change your mind. Any e-mail we send you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of that particular mailshot. Simply follow the indications in the e-mail.

Alternatively you can change your email preferences or opt out of all emails by logging into My Account.

**HOW YOU CAN ACCESS AND IF NECESSARY, CHANGE THE DATA STYLE MOI MAINTAINS**

If for any reason you are concerned that the Data held by Style Moi is not correct, please visit the website and, after logging into the site using the “Sign In” menu on the home page, your Data will be made available for review and change in the “My Account” section. Only you or, upon your request, the Customer Care department, may access your Data from the website using your password and User ID.

You may also change your shipping/billing addresses.

If you change your billing or shipping address while your order is still being processed, the order will be re-processed through security validation checks. If you prefer, you may contact us by email at support@stylemoi.nu and we will amend your Data.

**RETENTION OF DATA**

We will not keep your Data longer than is necessary for fulfilment of the purposes specified above for which they are, or are to be, used. Data provided by you is retained if the purpose for which the Data was collected still exists, it is so required by law, statute or regulation, or it is in the public interest.

**WHERE AND HOW TO ASK QUESTIONS OR FILE COMPLAINTS**

If you require more information please go to the Contact Us section of the web site and fill the on-line form or send an email to support@stylemoi.nu. If you wish to talk to a Style Moi customer care representative please call +852-81929558
